Akash Magar

IT Industry with 2.3 years of experience in ITIL and IT Service Management Solutions in IT Infrastructure. A ServiceNow expert with experience on implementing end-to-end Service Catalog, Configuration & Asset Management and Change Management with extensive knowledge on Content Management System.

EXPERIENCE

Cognizant Technology – Service Now Engineer

Feb 2022 - Present

Medtronic Administration (ServiceNow Engineer)

- 1. Created reports, workflows, data imports for Incident, Problem, Service Request, and Change Service Now Modules Experience in Implementing ServiceNow Discovery and CMDB and integration.
- 2. Created and Maintained foundation data User Accounts, Approvers, Support Groups, Sites, Production Categorizations, and Templates.
- 3. Responsible for preparing design level, program-level and user-level documentation.
- 4. Responsible for system development, project direction, process and roadmap guidance

Zeal Institute of Engineering - Teaching Assistant

Jan 2021 - July 2021 (0.7 yr)

- 1. Managing a student's size of 20+ people and assisting with day-to-day activities.
- 2. Responsible for Analyzing, reviewing, registering, scheduling training programs in PCB lab.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

ShopLane Web App

An E-commerce dynamic web app built with rendering dynamic product cards from GET API, add-to- cart functionality, place order POST API, functionality in checkout page.

Website: https://akashmagar703.github.io/JsShopLane/

To-Do App

App is created with functionalities like: Add, Edit, Update and Delete of To-Do items.

Website: https://akashmagar703.github.io/ToDo Web App/

Pune,
Maharashtra
+91 - 7709117592
akash.s.magar@gmail.com
LinkedIn:
https://www.linkedin.com/in/a
kash-magar-15-july/
GitHub:

https://github.com/akashmaga r703

SKILLS

ITSM
ServiceNow
CMDB
JavaScript
HTML5
CSS3
Data Management
Rest Api Services

EDUCATION

Master of Engineering (VLSI & Embedded System)

Zeal Institute of Engineering (2020–2022)

Bachelor of Engineering (Electronic & Telecommunication)

Deogiri Institute of Engineering (2017–2020)

CERTIFICATION

- Certified HTML, CSS & JavaScript for Web Developer Program in Johns Hopkins University, Coursera – 2021
- Certified ServiceNow
 Certified Application
 Developer 2024